<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Use Teleop on</title><link>https://doks-child-theme.netlify.app/vr/use-teleop/</link><description>Recent content in Use Teleop on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 09:01:14 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://doks-child-theme.netlify.app/vr/use-teleop/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Teleoperate Reachy</title><link>https://doks-child-theme.netlify.app/vr/use-teleop/start/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 09:01:49 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://doks-child-theme.netlify.app/vr/use-teleop/start/</guid><description>👉🏾 Before starting teleoperating Reachy, please make sure you read the Best Practice In brief #
👉 The button names used below are for the Meta Quest headsets. Please refer to the Controllers Input page to get the corresponding names for your device. Start teleoperating Reachy #
Make sure the robot is turned on, connected to the network and that all the robot&amp;rsquo;s services are running before launching the teleoperation application.</description></item><item><title>Teleoperation messages</title><link>https://doks-child-theme.netlify.app/vr/use-teleop/messages/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 09:01:43 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://doks-child-theme.netlify.app/vr/use-teleop/messages/</guid><description>During Reachy teleoperation, several messages can show up in front of view.
Warning messages
Some messages are just warnings, signaling you the quality of teleoperation may be altered or the current state of the robot may evolve into future errors (motors heating up or low battery). These messages are displayed on a dark grey background.
When possible, please consider acting to prevent these warnings from becoming errors.
Error messages
Other messages may signal errors, which will lead to a fast dysfunction of the teleoperation.</description></item><item><title>Commands</title><link>https://doks-child-theme.netlify.app/vr/use-teleop/commands/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 09:01:36 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://doks-child-theme.netlify.app/vr/use-teleop/commands/</guid><description>Oculus Quest #
Name Feature description A At robot teleoperation start: Start robot teleoperation During teleoperation: Return to menu B During teleoperation: Mobile base boost X During teleoperation: Open emotion menu (keep pressed) / Activate selected emotion (release) When leaving teleoperation (A pressed): Lock robot position Left Thumbstick During teleoperation: Control mobile base translation Right Thumbstick During teleoperation: Control mobile base rotation If emotion menu is open: Select emotion Left Index Trigger In menu: Select button During teleoperation: Control left gripper Right Index Trigger In menu: Select button During teleoperation: Control right gripper Left Controller position / orientation During teleoperation: Reachy&amp;rsquo;s left arm end effector position / orientation Right Controller position / orientation During teleoperation: Reachy&amp;rsquo;s right arm end effector position / orientation Headset orientation During teleoperation: Reachy&amp;rsquo;s head orientation Valve Index #
Name Feature description A right At robot teleoperation start: Start robot teleoperation During teleoperation: Return to menu A left During teleoperation: Open emotion menu (keep pressed) / Activate selected emotion (release) When leaving teleoperation (right A pressed): Lock robot position B right During teleoperation: Mobile base boost Left Thumbstick During teleoperation: Control mobile base translation Right Thumbstick During teleoperation: Control mobile base rotation If emotion menu is open: Select emotion Left Index Trigger In menu: Select button During teleoperation: Control left gripper Right Index Trigger In menu: Select button During teleoperation: Control right gripper Left Controller position / orientation During teleoperation: Reachy&amp;rsquo;s left arm end effector position / orientation Right Controller position / orientation During teleoperation: Reachy&amp;rsquo;s right arm end effector position / orientation Headset orientation During teleoperation: Reachy&amp;rsquo;s head orientation HTC Vive #
Name Feature description Sandwich menu right At robot teleoperation start: Start robot teleoperation During teleoperation: Return to menu Sandwich menu left During teleoperation: Open emotion menu (keep pressed) / Activate selected emotion (release) When leaving teleoperation (right menu pressed): Lock robot position Left Trackpad During teleoperation: Control mobile base translation Right Trackpad During teleoperation: Control mobile base rotation Center click: Mobile base boost If emotion menu is open: Select emotion Left Index Trigger In menu: Select button During teleoperation: Control left gripper Right Index Trigger In menu: Select button During teleoperation: Control right gripper Left Controller position / orientation During teleoperation: Reachy&amp;rsquo;s left arm end effector position / orientation Right Controller right position / orientation During teleoperation: Reachy&amp;rsquo;s right arm end effector position / orientation Headset orientation During teleoperation: Reachy&amp;rsquo;s head orientation</description></item><item><title>🚨 Best practice</title><link>https://doks-child-theme.netlify.app/vr/use-teleop/best-practice/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 09:01:27 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://doks-child-theme.netlify.app/vr/use-teleop/best-practice/</guid><description>👉🏾 This page contains really important information about the use of the teleoperation app. Please make sure you read it carefully before teleoperating Reachy. Using teleoperation application has nothing complicated, but you need to respect a few guidelines to avoid damaging the robot when using it. This page goes through the main elements you need to keep in mind while teleoperating Reachy. The guidelines are not exhaustive, but should give you a good start on how to safely use the application.</description></item></channel></rss>